Finding aid for the Universal Pictures Corporation Walter Lantz Productions scripts and music cue sheets, ca. 1947-1987 (bulk 1947-1965) LSC.1969
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Nos. 6-10, 12-13, and 15. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Nos. 17-21. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Nos. 22-27. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - cutting continuity scripts, no date (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Nos. 2-5. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - original continuity scripts, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Nos. 1-13. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - original continuity scripts, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Nos. 14-26. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker Show (The) - sequence and dialogue continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Nos. 27-52. Loose bound scripts with various segments for each show. Most segment titles are included.
- Woody Woodpecker TV Show - revised music cue sheets, 1973 Aug (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Woody Woodpecker TV Show - revised music cue sheets (folder 1 of 2), 1973 Aug (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Woody Woodpecker TV Show - revised music cue sheets (folder 2 of 2), 1973 Mar, 1975 Nov (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Woody's Clip Joint - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-175.
- Woody's Kook-Out - dialogue and cutting continuity scripts, c. 1961 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Walter Lantz Woody Woodpecker cartoon. Two copies. Original envelope annotated U-133.